India's first membership that covers all
medical expenses without hospitalization
get freedom from medical expenses in
just three simple steps download app
purchase membership upload medical
expenses every month without
hospitalization you will get all your
medical expenses reimbursed contact us
today and get icse and Lombard medical
insurance free as a gift
medical insurance companies take care of
your hospital related expenses
but the monthly expenses that you incur
on medicines and regular diseases that
nobody covers
medical reimbursement membership covers
those expenses which are not covered by
any medical insurance company
it doesn't matter if your expenses are
related to diabetes
or doctor visiting charges for
age-related problems or whether the cost
is for buying a mandate for your child's
wound
your expenses can be for a small or for
a big problem
mrm reimburses all medical expenses
without hospitalization
rather than spending your hard-earned
money on medicines and health related
issues mrm allows you to spend that
money on your family's happiness
mrm basic plan costs you 45 000 rupees
Plus jst
in which you get medical bills
reimbursement
three years of validity
up to 50 discount on medicines
monthly reimbursement of rupees 2000.
18 000 rupees renewable reward points
total benefit of rupees 90 000.
icse and Lombard medical insurance of
rupees 1 lakh as a gift
if your monthly medical expenses are
more than rupees two thousand then for
you we have mrm Advance plan which cost
you 90 000 rupees plus GST
in which you get medical bills
reimbursement
three years validity up to 50 discount
in medicines monthly reimbursement of
rupees 4 000.
36 000 rupees renewable reward points
total benefit of rupees one like eighty
thousand icse and low part medical
insurance of rupees 1 lakh as a gift
if your monthly expenses are more than
this then we can also personalize a plan
according to your needs
you can download our app from the
Android and iOS App Store
register
purchase membership
upload monthly medical expenses
get all your medical expenses reimbursed
in your bank account
we also deliver medicines at your
doorstep
with up to 50 discount
so what are you thinking
call us today and free your family from
all medical expenses
if you're looking forward to taking our
agency or working with us
then please get in touch